DELIVERANCE TIME
As the Evangelists sent by Prophet T.B. Joshua, minister the Morning Water to the congregation
at The Synagogue Church Of All Nations,
all the demonic chains in the lives of the people are being broken.
Every chain satan might have used to connect them to himself come loose in the mighty name of Jesus Christ.
Watch and see how this lady and her mother were delivered in Jesus' name.
In the mighty name of Jesus, in the blood of Jesus. Speak out, who are you?
Ministration of the Morning Water in Jesus' Name
You said you are who?
I am the spiritual husband.
Ok, how many of you are you in this body?
Stop it! Stop spraying!
How many of you are in this body? We don't have your time. How many of you are in this body?
How many of you?
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
Idol.
You said you are what?
As an idol and a spiritual husband, what have you done to her?
Stop it!
As an idol, speak out - what have you done to her?
I destroyed her and I want to kill her.
Her destiny is just too bright; I want to kill her.
How do you want to kill her - explain?
Her destiny is too bright; she wants to liberate the family.
What have you done to her career?
I don't want that.
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
Speak! What have you done to her career?
I put the spirit of anger in her.
She is very aggressive; I did it.
Don't spray that; I don't like it.
Open you eyes. Who is this woman beside you? Open your eyes!
Who is this woman beside you?
Who is she?
Her mother.
Madam, you are very welcome in Jesus' name.
Who is this lady?
She is my daughter.
What can you say about your daughter?
She has a bad character; she doesn't behave well.
She didn't finish school.
She gets sick and I have to rush her to the hospital.
Her father is an idol worshipper.
I rush her to the hospital every other day.
Who caused her all these setbacks?
Who is the cause?
It is me.
Right now, it is time for you to leave this body.
In the mighty name of Jesus, in the blood of Jesus - out!
Out!
In the mighty name of Jesus, Holy Ghost fire! All over your body.
From your head to your toes - Holy Ghost fire!
Fire!
Deliverance in Jesus' Name Through Ministration of the Morning Water
In the mighty name of Jesus. At the command in the blood of Jesus, out of this body!
You are going.
Out!
Deliverance in Jesus' Name Through Ministration of the Morning Water
Whatever you have deposited in this body, begin to remove them!
Remove the crown!
Remove the ring!
In the mighty name of Jesus, in the blood of Jesus.
Deliverance in Jesus' Name Through Ministration of the Morning Water
I command you out!
You said what?
There is something in my hair!
Remove it!
In the mighty name of Jesus, begin to remove it!
Whatever you have put on her head, that causes her setback -
Out!
In Jesus Christ's name!
Amen.
Sister, you have been set free today.
Through the medium of this Morning Water given to us by our Father in the Lord, Prophet T.B. Joshua,
you are free. Rise up!
Set Free in Jesus' Name
Thank You, Jesus!
Thank You, Jesus! Im free!
Madam, your daughter has been delivered today.
Do not remind her of what she has been delivered from today.
Otherwise, you shall be tempted.
Thank You, Jesus.
In the mighty name of Jesus, Holy Ghost fire!
Fire!
Speak out!
You demon, what have you done to her?
What have you caused this marriage?
What have you caused her family? Speak out!
Ministration of the Morning Water in Jesus' Name
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
Speak!
What have you done to her?
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
Speak out, who are you?
Speak, in the mighty name of Jesus!
Who are you in this body?
Who are you?
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
Holy Ghost fire!
On your toes!
Speak!
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
I am the spirit of anger.
You are spirit of what?
Anger.
Ok. As a spirit of anger, what have you done to her?
What have you done to her?
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
What else - speak!
She always quarrels.
What else have you made her to do?
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
I make people hate her; they always hate her.
Open your eyes, who is this lady beside you?
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
Who is she to you?
Speak out - who is she?
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
Sister, you are very welcome.
Who is this woman to you?
She is my mother.
What can you say about your mom?
She used to quarrel over any little thing.
People she helps, all turn back against her; no one is asking after her.
Everybody in the family hates her.
Who is the cause of that?
Who is the cause?
Speak! Who is the cause of that?
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
Who is the cause?
Anger.
How did you enter her?
How did you enter this body?
When she was small.
Ok. It is time for you to leave this body.
In the mighty name of Jesus, in the blood of Jesus - out!
Out!
In Jesus` name you are delivered,
through the medium of this Morning Water sent to you by our father in the Lord in Jesus' name.
Rise up!
Set Free in Jesus' Name
Congratulations. You have been set free and your daughter is free.
Thank You, Jesus!
Thank You, Jesus! I am free, my mother is free!
TESTIMONY TIME
Emmanuel! (God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Irabor Patience from Edo State.
The person standing beside me is my mother.
The other one is my elder brother, a graduate of Ambrose Alli University.
The other one is my cousin.
We all came here for our deliverance.
This spiritual husband had really affected me and my career.
Can you start by telling us what you were delivered from?
I was delivered from a spiritual husband, the spirit of idol from my father's house.
and from the spirit of prostitution.
This idol had really disturbed me.
We were all born into an idol family.
My father was an idol worshipper.
The thing had really disturbed us.
Ever since my dad died, the idol had been tormenting the children.
We had all become scattered and nothing was going well for us.
My brother who is a graduate, nothing was going well for him.
My sister out there was suffering.
I was also suffering.
I managed to enter school.
When I was in school, I moved with friends and went out to clubs
because the spiritual husband had really tormented me.
Was this at secondary school or university?
It was at university.
My mum was complaining that things were not working well for her.
What used to happen to you when you were at university?
When I was at university, I was not living a good life.
This spirit had really tormented me.
Each time I was in school, the evil spirit would push me to go out with men for money -
just to get money to take care of myself and my family because of the predicament in the home.
We had been suffering.
What about other members of the family?
My sister also went out to Malaysia, just to get a means for us to survive.
But still, she went there and was doing the same thing - prostitution.
It really affected us.
My sister called my mum one day and asked her if we had heard of The SCOAN
that we should come to The SCOAN because she was tired of everything.
She said she was suffering there and didn't want to live that kind of life anymore.
That was how we came to The SCOAN and were all delivered last Sunday.
Tell us - when the Morning Water was being ministered to you, what did you feel at that moment?
When the Morning Water was ministered to me at that moment,
I felt something in me trying to come out.
I felt fire in me; something was burning inside me. I felt heat all over my body.
That was how I came out, manifested and was delivered.
Since your deliverance, can you tell us what the changes are that have taken place in your life?
Since my deliverance, I sleep well.
I don't have the urge to go out with men anymore.
I sleep well. I have good dreams. I don't have the urge of going out to sleep with men anymore.
I am delivered now.
Shall we put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Morning Water Testimony
Apart from going out with men, what were other attitudes, behaviours and habits you developed then?
When I was in school, I used to go to clubs, drink with my friends, go to parties and go out with men.
That was not the kind of life I wanted for myself.
The spirit in me had really tormented me.
Since after your deliverance, do you still have the urge to drink alcohol?
No, I don't have the urge to take alcohol or to go out with men anymore.
Once again, let us put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Irabor Patience & Family - Morning Water Testimony
We thank God.
Before we listen to your word of advice, let us hear from your mother who was also delivered.
Irabor Patience & Family - Morning Water Testimony
Madam, can you please tell us your name and your own side of the testimony.
Emmanuel! (God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Tessy Irabor.
I'm from Edo State.
Tessy & Family - Edo, Nigeria
She is my daughter.
This is my son.
The other one is my sister's daugther.
Really, I married an idol worshipper.
The idol worshipping was fighting against us.
The spiritual husband was working against me - everything.
We didn't even know where we were going.
My daughter travelled to Malaysia for prostitution.
This of mine who graduated - no work.
This one was doing her own thing.
When my daughter called me, she asked me if I knew The SCOAN. I said, "Yes".
She said that there was a problem.
I told her my own was a problem -
that my market had gone down and that I couldn't even see anything to eat in the house.
Then, my daughter told me that I should be ready to come to The SCOAN.
I told her I didn't have the transport fare.
She made a face and brought out money.
When she brought the money, I struggled to collect the money from her to give people I owed.
My daughter insisted us coming to the SCOAN.
That was how we came for deliverance.
I thank God that my children are delivered and I am delivered, in the name of Jesus.
Shall we put our hands together for Jesus!
Tessy & Family - Morning Water Testimony
Tell us - since after your deliverance, how has your life and everything else been?
Since my deliverance, I sleep well and I am very happy.
I told my son and my daughter that I sleep very well now.
I am very happy.
What word of advice do you have for people who are listening to your testimony?
The advice I want to give people concerning this kind of problem I entered
with an idol worshipper is that before you give your daughter to any man,
watch the house and check whether there are any idols there.
If an idol is there, pray, so that God would deliver you.
Tessy & Family - Morning Water Testimony
Ok.
So that is the advice that we should watch out before we jump!
We thank God Almighty for everything.
Now the family is delivered to the glory of God.
We would like to hear from our brother as well.
Irabor Patience & Family - Morning Water Testimony
Tell us your name.
My name is Irabor Frank.
We are from Edo State.
This is my mother, my younger sister and my little cousin.
I thank God that my family is delivered from idol worship.
I really noticed it in my mum because in those days, if I told her a little thing,
she would get annoyed.
After her deliverance on Sunday, we got home. We were just talking.
There was a word I was using but she didn't even pick on me; she just talked and smiled.
I said, "Wow! Thank God, we are really delivered!"
Emmanuel! My family is delivered!
Amen.
Tell us how this idol affected your own personal life? What are the challenges you have been facing?
It had really affected me.
When I graduated during my NYSC,
I met some people who said they were going to help me after my NYSC.
But immediately I finished my NYSC, I misplaced my phone and I didn't see them again.
The last one I met said that he would see what he could do but up to now - nothing.
So you mean since you graduated, there's nothing to show for it?
Nothing.
Now the family is delivered, your past is over and your breakthrough is restored.
Amen.
Let us clap for Jesus!
Frank & Family - Morning Water Testimony
Morning Water Testimony
Finally, can we hear a word of advice from you
to young ones like yourself and also to parents?
My advice to my fellow youth is that we should not look at other people on the outside.
I am dressed like this - seeing me dressed like this, you would feel that I had it all.
No, I did not have it all; I was burning inside because I could not stop it.
I thank God that I am delivered.
If you have the same problem as I had, the only thing I will tell you is for you to run to Christ
because He is the only One who can save us.
Amen.
Irabor Patience & Family - Morning Water Testimony
Indeed, only Jesus Christ can save.
He is the answer to all fundamental issues of life.
Now that you and the entire family are delivered, we want to encourage you
to stay true to our Lord Jesus Christ, make the Word of God the standard for your life and your family
and embrace the wonderful Word of God as the most effective instrument for change.
As you do so, the breakthrough and blessings of God Almighty will begin to unfold
and you will come back to testify to this, in Jesus' name.
Amen.
Put your hands together for Jesus Christ!